<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
    
    <DropComment>Comment from the imperial caterer:</DropComment>
    
    <!-- Ресурсы -->
    <DropComment_SteelDrop>Ore is the basis of civilisation. As long as you have the iron to make steel, life is not so bad.</DropComment_SteelDrop>
    <DropComment_SilverDrop>Everyone needs money, no matter how much. In whatever form they may be.</DropComment_SilverDrop>
    <DropComment_IndustrialMetalsDrop>These metals will allow you to build a society on even the most miserable death world, should there be a need.</DropComment_IndustrialMetalsDrop>
    <DropComment_PreciousMetalsDrop>Expensive, valuable and not needed by most people. This is what these materials have in common.</DropComment_PreciousMetalsDrop>
    <DropComment_FoodDrop>Everyone needs food. Well, almost everyone, I still get the shivers from those humanoid robots. Oh, and yes, don't forget to put the food away from your pets straight away.</DropComment_FoodDrop>
    <DropComment_GlitterMedDrop>Is there a problem? We have an extensive supply of medical equipment, and I'd be happy to share, but do you know how many of you there are? We don't have enough for everyone, so we don't have to send very much.</DropComment_GlitterMedDrop>
    <DropComment_BlocksDrop>What? These cobblestones? What do you use them for, paving streets or something? In Fortuna, we only find them in old squares. Anyway, it's up to you.</DropComment_BlocksDrop>
    <DropComment_CallTransportShuttle>Need something moved? You are welcome, I will send you a bird.</DropComment_CallTransportShuttle>
    <DropComment_ClothDrop>Usually synthread is cheaper than natural fabric, but we've had a whole planet-farm recently integrated, tons of stuff available again.</DropComment_ClothDrop>
    <DropComment_WoolDrop>Usually synthread is cheaper than natural leather and wool, but we've had a whole planet-farm recently integrated, tons of stuff available again.</DropComment_WoolDrop>
    <DropComment_WoodDrop>Usually plastic and metals is cheaper than natural wood, but we've had a whole planet-farm recently integrated, tons of stuff available again.</DropComment_WoodDrop>
    <DropComment_ComponentsDrop>Parts, gears, pistons, something else... Figure it out for yourself.</DropComment_ComponentsDrop>
    <DropComment_ChemicalsDrop>It's some sort of chemicals I don't recognize. I'll tell the packers to pack this stuff better.</DropComment_ChemicalsDrop>
    <DropComment_SerumsDrop>The pinnacle of technology in our world. I only know about them because of my work. Instant healing and resurrection is a dangerously powerful resource.</DropComment_SerumsDrop>

    <!-- Люди -->
    <DropComment_CallLaborerTeam>Not enough hands? We have a selection of low-skilled workers from the lower levels of the planet just for you!</DropComment_CallLaborerTeam>
    <DropComment_CallLaborerGang>Are you not satisfied with the stack of workers we've already provided? Well, we can just offer more of them, we can't send you our specialists.</DropComment_CallLaborerGang>
    <DropComment_CallMilitaryAidSmall>Are you being attacked by local tribes? Fortunately we have no such thing here. To solve this problem, I am able to provide you with selected soldiers of the Imperial Guard, fresh out of training school without any qualifications!</DropComment_CallMilitaryAidSmall>
    <DropComment_CallMilitaryAidSmallPlus>Are there so many raiders that you don't have enough soldiers? So have more soldiers, that always solves the problem!</DropComment_CallMilitaryAidSmallPlus>
    <DropComment_CallMilitaryAidLarge>Can't the young boys in the guard do the job against the pirates? We have local elite mercenary units who will destroy any target for a penny!</DropComment_CallMilitaryAidLarge>
    <DropComment_CallMilitaryAidGrand>Is it that bad? If you are allowed that kind of privilege, there is no problem that the elite units of the Imperial Guard can't handle. The main thing is not to let them into your prison, you just shouldn't.</DropComment_CallMilitaryAidGrand>

    <!-- Артобстрел -->
    <DropComment_CallOrbitalStrike>A bomb dropped in time in a cluster of enemies solves the need for additional soldiers.</DropComment_CallOrbitalStrike>
    <DropComment_CallOrbitalSalvo>Lots of bombs dropped in time to a cluster of enemies solves the problems of the need to allocate soldiers to the front as a whole.</DropComment_CallOrbitalSalvo>

    <!-- Животные -->
    <DropComment_MilkAnimalDrop>Everybody loves milk. I wish I had a bottle of goat's milk right now.....</DropComment_MilkAnimalDrop>
    <DropComment_EggAnimalDrop>An egg for breakfast and go to work.</DropComment_EggAnimalDrop>
    <DropComment_WoolAnimalDrop>Natural wool is a valuable commodity, but here we have nowhere to graze these animals.....</DropComment_WoolAnimalDrop>
    <DropComment_MeatAnimalDrop>Natural meat is very hard to get, we have mostly plant-based everything here. I wish I could afford more of it....</DropComment_MeatAnimalDrop>
    <DropComment_CaravanAnimalDrop>Caravan animals? Well, I have to call another caterer, we don't have one here. I'll be in touch if you need me.</DropComment_CaravanAnimalDrop>
    <DropComment_BattleAnimalDrop>Fighting beasts are barely used in the Empire, so don't count on trained beasts. However, just suitable animals are available, can be arranged.</DropComment_BattleAnimalDrop>
    <DropComment_PetAnimalDrop>Do you want a pet? We have plenty of them, the best breeds! I would even give them away for free, but the clerk's office is against it.</DropComment_PetAnimalDrop>
    <DropComment_ExoticAnimalDrop>Exotic... And why is everyone with any influence interested in them? The possibility of supply is there, but I don't recommend it, you'd better look for something else.</DropComment_ExoticAnimalDrop>
    <DropComment_MythicalAnimalDrop>Mythical beasts... Can you send me a picture later?</DropComment_MythicalAnimalDrop>
    <DropComment_MountsAnimalDrop>Do you want to become a rider? All the nobles of the Empire know how to ride, so you should learn too!</DropComment_MountsAnimalDrop>
    <DropComment_SpiderAnimalDrop>Spiders? Seriously? I wouldn't even go near them, and you want to live with them? You're insane.</DropComment_SpiderAnimalDrop>

    <!-- Одежда -->
    <DropComment_SmithOutfitDrop>Clothes for the blacksmith? I don't have the slightest idea what's supposed to be there, so I clarify... Oh, I see, it's easy to arrange.</DropComment_SmithOutfitDrop>
    <DropComment_FarmerOutfitDrop>Clothes for the farmer? I don't have the slightest idea what's supposed to be there, so I clarify... Oh, I see, it's easy to arrange.</DropComment_FarmerOutfitDrop>
    <DropComment_ChefOutfitDrop>Clothes for the chef? I don't have the slightest idea what's supposed to be there, so I clarify... Oh, I see, it's easy to arrange.</DropComment_ChefOutfitDrop>
    <DropComment_MedicOutfitDrop>Clothing for the doctor? We have a lot of medical gear, it's not a problem to find something.</DropComment_MedicOutfitDrop>
    <DropComment_MinerOutfitDrop>Clothes for the miner? I don't have the slightest idea what's supposed to be there, so I clarify... Oh, I see, it's easy to arrange.</DropComment_MinerOutfitDrop>
    <DropComment_ConstructorOutfitDrop>Clothes for the constructor? I don't have the slightest idea what's supposed to be there, so I clarify... Oh, I see, it's easy to arrange.</DropComment_ConstructorOutfitDrop>
    <DropComment_SlaveOutfitDrop>Clothes for a slave? Do they need specific clothes at all? Well, we'll send you something appropriate.</DropComment_SlaveOutfitDrop>
    <DropComment_HazmatOutfitDrop>Chemical protection? What are you doing out there that needs chemical protection? You'd better not violate the galactic code now that you're part of the Empire. But if anything, I didn't see anything.</DropComment_HazmatOutfitDrop>
    <DropComment_RoyalOutfitDrop>Clothes for the nobility. We have our own particular style of clothing on Fortuna, if you want, I'll request a full set. Quality is guaranteed.</DropComment_RoyalOutfitDrop>
    <DropComment_PsychicOutfitDrop>Clothes for psykers? They' re respectable people, of course, but a lot of people are afraid of them, so even famous psykers prefer not to advertise their abilities. However, it is your right, we are ready to provide you with a set.</DropComment_PsychicOutfitDrop>
    <DropComment_SimpleOutfitDrop>Simple clothes for simple folks. We have plenty of those.</DropComment_SimpleOutfitDrop>

    <!-- Броня -->
    <DropComment_ArmorDrop>What is bacinet? Never mind, just redirecting the request.</DropComment_ArmorDrop>
    <DropComment_ArmorDropPlus>Seriously? Bacinet made of ferrotitanium? Your choice, but that seems like an odd use of material to me.</DropComment_ArmorDropPlus>
    <DropComment_IndustrialArmorDrop>The classic armor of our new colonies. We always have one set ready to ship, specify your body size.</DropComment_IndustrialArmorDrop>
    <DropComment_IndustrialArmorDropPlus>Hmm, improved classic colonial armor? I would recommend just ordering something better, but suit yourself.</DropComment_IndustrialArmorDropPlus>
    <DropComment_SpacerArmorDrop>Now that's a great choice, you have taste. Imperial Guard armor is reliable and easy to handle, and we always have a huge supply of repaired armor after battles with mechanoids!</DropComment_SpacerArmorDrop>
    <DropComment_SpacerArmorDropPlus>A kit of the highest officers of the Imperial Guard. Normally you can't get such kits, but many kits created on Vulcan go through Fortuna, so I'm willing to arrange one for you.</DropComment_SpacerArmorDropPlus>
    <DropComment_UltraArmorDrop>I would have to go to the Capital Office on Juno for permission to issue such a suite. It is indeed one of the finest armors in the Empire, produced only on Vulcan, and only some of the most titled people in the Empire receive it.</DropComment_UltraArmorDrop>
    <DropComment_UltraArmorDropPlus>An upgraded set of ultra armor? I have no right to even apply for it, I refer you directly to the Capital Office...</DropComment_UltraArmorDropPlus>
    <DropComment_SoldierAccessoriesDrop>Ah, stormtrooper gear. If your guard needs extra gear besides armor, that's your choice. That one won't take bullets, not like these scouts.</DropComment_SoldierAccessoriesDrop>
    <DropComment_SoldierAccessoriesAltDrop>Ah, scouting gear. It's always good to have guards who can react quickly to threats, because all those stormtroopers are so slow...</DropComment_SoldierAccessoriesAltDrop>
    <DropComment_ShieldBeltDrop>Shield belt, useful thing, saved a lot of people, so we always have a reserve. Shall I prepare it for shipment?</DropComment_ShieldBeltDrop>
    <DropComment_ShieldHeavyBeltDrop>Shield belt, useful thing, saved a lot of people, so we always have a reserve. Shall I prepare it for shipment?</DropComment_ShieldHeavyBeltDrop>
    <DropComment_ShieldQRBeltDrop>Shield belt, useful thing, saved a lot of people, so we always have a reserve. Shall I prepare it for shipment?</DropComment_ShieldQRBeltDrop>
    <DropComment_ShieldRangedBeltDrop>Ranged belt-shield is a relatively new technology, so I have an outright ban on giving these samples to certain titles.</DropComment_ShieldRangedBeltDrop>

    <!-- Инструменты -->
    <DropComment_ToolDrop>A set of tools? Well, that's never too much to ask, especially if you give them out to the slaves on the plantations.</DropComment_ToolDrop>
    <DropComment_ToolDropPlus>Do you want durable tools? Well, that's not hard to arrange. It's not a bad thing to work with such a tool yourself.</DropComment_ToolDropPlus>
    <DropComment_AdvToolDrop>The Multitool is a tool of the workers of the Empire's core. They do not appear often outside of it, but you can request one.</DropComment_AdvToolDrop>
    <DropComment_AdvToolDropPlus>The Multitool from AdvancedMachines™ is the best multitool available for purchase. The Empire buys them in whole lots, so you can get one, too.</DropComment_AdvToolDropPlus>
    <DropComment_PlantsWorkerDrop>As you sow, so shall you reap.</DropComment_PlantsWorkerDrop>
    <DropComment_MinerWorkerDrop>A smart man will not go up or around the mountain - a smart man will dismantle it and build a palace out of it.</DropComment_MinerWorkerDrop>
    <DropComment_BuilderWorkerDrop>Every man is the architect of his own fortune.</DropComment_BuilderWorkerDrop>
    <DropComment_CraftsmanWorkerDrop>Forge your future. And also titanium, stellite, and God knows how many other things you don't need to know about.</DropComment_CraftsmanWorkerDrop>.
    <DropComment_MedicWorkerDrop>The cost of a surgeon's mistake is always too high. These tools allow you to buy the chance of survival.</DropComment_MedicWorkerDrop>
    <DropComment_JanitorWorkerDrop>Are you sure you need this? Are you sure?</DropComment_JanitorWorkerDrop>.
    <DropComment_ScientistWorkerDrop>Most importantly, do not install games on this PDA.</DropComment_ScientistWorkerDrop>

    <!-- Турели -->
    <DropComment_BallistaDrop>Ballistas? Why do you need them, just get something better.</DropComment_BallistaDrop>
    <DropComment_CatapultDrop>Catapults... We're way past that, aren't we? But if you want, I'll leave a request, our craftsmen can build anything.</DropComment_CatapultDrop>
    <DropComment_MG1LightTurretDrop>Stationary machine guns are nice, but aren't they obsolete? Everything comes with auto-fire and a friend-or-foe system now, so why do you need a conventional machine gun?</DropComment_MG1LightTurretDrop>
    <DropComment_MG1HeavyTurretDrop>Stationary machine guns are nice, but aren't they obsolete? Everything comes with auto-fire and a friend-or-foe system now, so why do you need a conventional machine gun?</DropComment_MG1HeavyTurretDrop>
    <DropComment_MG2LightTurretDrop>Stationary machine guns are nice, but aren't they obsolete? Everything comes with auto-fire and a friend-or-foe system now, so why do you need a conventional machine gun, even if it's a pretty good one?</DropComment_MG2LightTurretDrop>
    <DropComment_MG2HeavyTurretDrop>Stationary machine guns are nice, but aren't they obsolete? Everything comes with auto-fire and a friend-or-foe system now, so why do you need a conventional machine gun, even if it's a pretty good one?</DropComment_MG2HeavyTurretDrop>
    <DropComment_AGS17TurretDrop>Stationary grenade launchers? That's interesting, I've never heard of them. If you order one, send me a video from the firing range!</DropComment_AGS17TurretDrop>
    <DropComment_AGS30TurretDrop>Another stationary grenade launcher, only bigger and better. I wonder how scary it is to go up against it...</DropComment_AGS30TurretDrop>
    <DropComment_A81MortarDrop>Mortars are a cool thing. Getting rid of enemies before encountering them. Too bad accuracy suffers.</DropComment_A81MortarDrop>
    <DropComment_A90MortarDrop>The bigger the mortar, the bigger the explosion!</DropComment_A90MortarDrop>
    <DropComment_A120MortarDrop>Is it still a mortar or is it artillery?</DropComment_A120MortarDrop>
    <DropComment_A155MortarDrop>Beautiful thing, the last artillery used by the Empire before switching to ballistic missiles.</DropComment_A155MortarDrop>
    <DropComment_JavelinTurretDrop>A short-range missile system. No average raider would be able to get past one of these.</DropComment_JavelinTurretDrop>
    <DropComment_TOWTurretDrop>A short-range missile system. No average raider would be able to get past one of these.</DropComment_TOWTurretDrop>
    <DropComment_MediumRKDrop>An advanced missile system that destroys entire enemy squads. Cool stuff, I wish I'd have seen it in action.</DropComment_MediumRKDrop>
    <DropComment_HeavyRKDrop>The largest missile system available for delivery by the Empire. I highly recommend stocking up on ammunition.</DropComment_HeavyRKDrop>
    <DropComment_LightAutoTurretDrop>A miniature auto-turret. Already not bad, but the small caliber prevents it from reaching its potential.</DropComment_LightAutoTurretDrop>
    <DropComment_HeavyAutoTurretDrop>A full-fledged auto-turret. I always liked these turrets, no unnecessary overhangs, plenty of ammo for them, what more do you need.</DropComment_HeavyAutoTurretDrop>
    <DropComment_BigLightAutoTurretDrop>An automatic homing missile system. What else can I say - one missile can cancel the whole raid.</DropComment_BigLightAutoTurretDrop>
    <DropComment_BigHeavyAutoTurretDrop>This turret, if you can call it that, used to be installed on naval warships. Nowadays such ships are rare, but the turret is still effective. But it used to require manual operation, and now they've added automation, you know what that means, don't you?</DropComment_BigHeavyAutoTurretDrop>
    <DropComment_HighTechLightAutoTurretDrop>The latest innovations in autoturret production! This plasma turret gets rid of your enemies not only figuratively, but literally as well!</DropComment_HighTechLightAutoTurretDrop>
    <DropComment_HighTechHeavyAutoTurretDrop>The latest innovations in autoturret production! This laser turret is extremely accurate and long-range, which allows it to shoot even snipers.</DropComment_HighTechHeavyAutoTurretDrop>

    <!-- Ближний бой -->
    <DropComment_AgileMeleeDrop>Do you like lighter weapons? I don't know why you need them, but we'll provide them.</DropComment_AgileMeleeDrop>
    <DropComment_AgileMeleeDropPlus>The best craftsmen and quality materials, and your weapons will carry the light of the Emperor to all parts of the galaxy even more effectively!</DropComment_AgileMeleeDropPlus>
    <DropComment_SharpMeleeDrop>Cutting enemies is always more pleasant with a sharp weapon. The main thing is to get close to the enemy with it.</DropComment_SharpMeleeDrop>
    <DropComment_SharpMeleeDropPlus>The best craftsmen and quality materials, and your weapons will carry the light of the Emperor to all parts of the galaxy even more effectively!</DropComment_SharpMeleeDropPlus>
    <DropComment_BluntMeleeDrop>Hit hard... That's kind of barbaric. The only way that would work is with mechanoids, but no one in the Empire fights with them without EMP rounds, lasers, or plasma.</DropComment_BluntMeleeDrop>
    <DropComment_BluntMeleeDropPlus>The best craftsmen and quality materials, and your weapons will carry the light of the Emperor to all parts of the galaxy even more effectively!</DropComment_BluntMeleeDropPlus>
    <DropComment_HeavyMeleeDrop>Heavy weapons are always a powerful argument. An acquaintance of mine told me how he suppressed a riot on the Aurora, the imperial knights were suppressing everyone with one sight of their weapons.</DropComment_HeavyMeleeDrop>
    <DropComment_HeavyMeleeDropPlus>The best craftsmen and quality materials, and your weapons will carry the light of the Emperor to all parts of the galaxy even more effectively!</DropComment_HeavyMeleeDropPlus>
    <DropComment_EODBladeDrop>Monoblades are one of the best types of blades of modern times. Blades of a more civilized era, which are now produced only in the main and most advanced manufactoriums. You should definitely get one.</DropComment_EODBladeDrop>
    <DropComment_EODBladePlusDrop>Monoblades are one of the best types of blades of modern times. And it also includes a combat AI. Blades of a more civilized era, which are now produced only in the main and most advanced manufactoriums. You should definitely get one.</DropComment_EODBladePlusDrop>

    <!-- Дальний бой -->
    <DropComment_BowDrop>If you need it, you can have it. The only reason we can't give it away for free is because of shipping. We got a warehouse full of stuff, but they won't let us just throw it in the furnace. But we'll give you more arrows.</DropComment_BowDrop>
    <DropComment_BowDropPlus>Among all the junk there are better models. It takes a little longer to find them in warehouses, but they are also ready to give them away for almost nothing.</DropComment_BowDropPlus>
    <DropComment_PistolDrop>Pistols are an underrated weapon. It is always faster to draw a sidearm than to reload a weapon.</DropComment_PistolDrop>
    <DropComment_PistolDropPlus>The best craftsmen and quality materials, and your weapons will carry the light of the Emperor to all parts of the galaxy even more effectively!</DropComment_PistolDropPlus>
    <DropComment_SMGDrop>Submachine guns are compact boxes of death, which for some reason are rather rarely requested from us. It's even a bit of a shame.</DropComment_SMGDrop>
    <DropComment_SMGDropPlus>The best craftsmen and quality materials, and your weapons will carry the light of the Emperor to all parts of the galaxy even more effectively!</DropComment_SMGDropPlus>
    <DropComment_ShotgunDrop>Shotguns are a great thing! But for some reason nobody takes them at all, and they say something about shooting at point-blank range. Do they not know about the range of the shotgun?</DropComment_ShotgunDrop>
    <DropComment_ShotgunDropPlus>The best craftsmen and quality materials, and your weapons will carry the light of the Emperor to all parts of the galaxy even more effectively!</DropComment_ShotgunDropPlus>
    <DropComment_RifleDrop>Assault and combat rifles have been combat classics for thousands of years. It's true that the Empire switched to energy weapons not so long ago, so don't be surprised if your weapons are not factory-quality but have already been in combat.</DropComment_RifleDrop>
    <DropComment_RifleDropPlus>The best craftsmen and quality materials, and your weapons will carry the light of the Emperor to all parts of the galaxy even more effectively!</DropComment_RifleDropPlus>
    <DropComment_SniperRifleDrop>Sniper rifles are works of art among weapons. Deadly and unforgiving of mistakes, they are the apotheosis of firearms, though not everyone agrees on this.</DropComment_SniperRifleDrop>
    <DropComment_SniperRifleDropPlus>The best craftsmen and quality materials, and your weapons will carry the light of the Emperor to all parts of the galaxy even more effectively!</DropComment_SniperRifleDropPlus>
    <DropComment_MGDrop>Machine guns are the perfect thing for crowd control. It's enough just to start firing, and the number of bullets suppresses everyone except the mechanoids. But there are EMP rounds for them.</DropComment_MGDrop>
    <DropComment_MGDropPlus>The best craftsmen and quality materials, and your weapons will carry the light of the Emperor to all parts of the galaxy even more effectively!</DropComment_MGDropPlus>
    <DropComment_LauncherDrop>Grenade launchers and rocket launchers are extremely dangerous toys. Be careful with them, I like talking to you.</DropComment_LauncherDrop>
    <DropComment_LauncherDropPlus>The best craftsmen and quality materials, and your weapons will carry the light of the Emperor to all parts of the galaxy even more effectively!</DropComment_LauncherDropPlus>
    <DropComment_BlasterDrop>Blasters are cool. Accuracy is worse than lasers, but if you start spraying the entire battlefield, it doesn't matter who the enemy is - it melts them all!</DropComment_BlasterDrop>
    <DropComment_LasersDrop>Lasers are an extremely delicate matter. On the one hand in the hands of a professional they are more effective than blasters, on the other hand in major battles they are not as good in average - they lack the intimidating effect of plasmers and blasters.</DropComment_LasersDrop>
    <DropComment_PlasmerDrop>Plasmers are the best category of weapon in my opinion. Although there is a fairly even distribution of energy weapons in the Empire, I personally asked to be issued with a service plasmer.</DropComment_PlasmerDrop>
    <DropComment_ChargeRailDrop>Energy rifles are rare even among special units, because they require much more skill than any other weapon. Not everyone can handle them, and Railgun recoil is sometimes used as a test for some prospective soldiers on what type of weapon is suits for them.</DropComment_ChargeRailDrop>

    <!-- Боеприпасы -->
    <DropComment_PistolAmmoDrop>Simple ammo for simple people.</DropComment_PistolAmmoDrop>
    <DropComment_ShotgunAmmoDrop>Always useful if you need to pacify a crowd.</DropComment_ShotgunAmmoDrop>
    <DropComment_SmallRifleAmmoDrop>The gold standard of gunsmithing in a compact version. Take it, there will always be a gun to it.</DropComment_SmallRifleAmmoDrop>
    <DropComment_MediumRifleAmmoDrop>The gold standard of gunsmithing in a powerful version. Take it, there will always be a gun to it.</DropComment_MediumRifleAmmoDrop>
    <DropComment_BigRifleAmmoDrop>In case the powerful one is no longer enough, there is always these one. But usually for such calibers it is better to make weapons yourself or request them from our warehouses.</DropComment_BigRifleAmmoDrop>
    <DropComment_GiantRifleAmmoDrop>For the most extreme cases where size is very important.</DropComment_GiantRifleAmmoDrop>
    <DropComment_GrenadesAmmoDrop>Throwing explosions at problems is always the solution.</DropComment_GrenadesAmmoDrop>
    <DropComment_RocketsAmmoDrop>...And if the explosions have to hit far away, add engines to them!</DropComment_RocketsAmmoDrop>
    <DropComment_FuelAmmoDrop>And let the world burn. Or at least the part of it that's against you.</DropComment_FuelAmmoDrop>
    <DropComment_ShellsAmmoDrop>Sometimes changing the landscape can involve an unusual approach and creative...</DropComment_ShellsAmmoDrop>
    <DropComment_ChargedAmmoDrop>New generation calibers hit harder, fly faster, penetrate better, but the feeling is not the same....</DropComment_ChargedAmmoDrop>
    <DropComment_EnergyAmmoDrop>Shooting pure energy has been a dream of humans for millennia, now such weapons are everywhere, they are powerful, but the dream feels shattered from the final reality...</DropComment_EnergyAmmoDrop>
    <DropComment_MagAmmoDrop>Found recently in the ruins of the forge planet, these prototype cartridges have been reconstructed and are now spreading across the galaxy once again.</DropComment_MagAmmoDrop>

    <!-- Семена -->
    <DropComment_SeedsGrainsDrop>Grains in any kind are the best breakfast both on the core planets and on the Rim! But we don't have them much here.</DropComment_SeedsGrainsDrop>
    <DropComment_SeedsVegesDrop>Vegetables are the perfect lunch. Healthy and sometimes even nourishing. It's a pity there are not so many of them on Fortuna...</DropComment_SeedsVegesDrop>
    <DropComment_SeedsShroomsDrop>Mushrooms are delicious. Too bad I have an intolerance, I would only eat them.....</DropComment_SeedsShroomsDrop>
    <DropComment_SeedsLuxDrop>It's got all these things in the kit that are for haute cuisine. I have no idea what half of this list is for.</DropComment_SeedsLuxDrop>
    <DropComment_SeedsAddictiveDrop>We can certainly provide these, but only if you sign forms 28M/13-23, 13G-14POT, and 8RTV/G#231.</DropComment_SeedsAddictiveDrop>
    <DropComment_SeedsClothDrop>Fabric made from plant fibers is expensive on this world. I suppose you have a similar situation with synthetics.....</DropComment_SeedsClothDrop>
    <DropComment_SeedsHealDrop>Plant medicine? Is that even possible?</DropComment_SeedsHealDrop>
    <DropComment_SeedsUtilDrop>I'll be honest - I have no idea what it is. Check the list for yourself.</DropComment_SeedsUtilDrop>
    <DropComment_SeedsTreeDrop>Trees... Eh, I wish there were more trees, sometimes all this concrete and metal luster is very annoying.</DropComment_SeedsTreeDrop>
    <DropComment_SeedsFruitDrop>Fruit is not often seen on our table, the most delicious fruits are a whole delicacy.</DropComment_SeedsFruitDrop>

    <!-- Протезы -->
    <DropComment_SimpleProsthetic>Simple prosthetics for all life's challenges.</DropComment_SimpleProsthetic>
    <DropComment_BionicsProsthetic>Bionics are quite common on the worlds of the central segmentum, but almost none are produced in your, so shipping is a bit difficult.</DropComment_BionicsProsthetic>
    <DropComment_CyberneticProsthetic>The best prosthetics in the entire empire - we don't have very many in our stock, all on demand in small batches.</DropComment_CyberneticProsthetic>
    <DropComment_CombatProsthetic>Do you need to improve your soldiers? This will help.</DropComment_CombatProsthetic>
    <DropComment_CombatImplants>Do you need to improve your soldiers? This will help.</DropComment_CombatImplants>
    <DropComment_CombatImplantsAdvanced>The best combat implants for personal protection of titled persons.</DropComment_CombatImplantsAdvanced>
    <DropComment_ProductionProsthetic>Do you need to improve your workers? This will help.</DropComment_ProductionProsthetic>
    <DropComment_ProductionImplants>Do you need to improve your workers? This will help.</DropComment_ProductionImplants>
    <DropComment_ProductionImplantsAdvanced>The best work performance enhancement implants for the best servants of titled persons.</DropComment_ProductionImplantsAdvanced>

    <!-- Колонисты -->
    <DropComment_ColonistShootingDrop>Any self-respecting nobleman should have a personal guard.</DropComment_ColonistShootingDrop>
    <DropComment_ColonistMeleeDrop>Any self-respecting nobleman should have a personal guard.</DropComment_ColonistMeleeDrop>
    <DropComment_ColonistConstructionDrop>Somebody has to build you a palace, right?</DropComment_ColonistConstructionDrop>
    <DropComment_ColonistMiningDrop>Somebody has to mine the materials for your palace (better yet, just order from us), right?</DropComment_ColonistMiningDrop>
    <DropComment_ColonistCookingDrop>Somebody has to be your personal chef (you can order food from us, but it will arrive cold), right?</DropComment_ColonistCookingDrop>
    <DropComment_ColonistPlantsDrop>Somebody has to grow food for your personal chef's kitchen, right?</DropComment_ColonistPlantsDrop>
    <DropComment_ColonistAnimalsDrop>Somebody has to grow meat for your personal chef's kitchen, right?</DropComment_ColonistAnimalsDrop>
    <DropComment_ColonistCraftingDrop>Somebody has to make you a crown and sew you velvet robes, right?</DropComment_ColonistCraftingDrop>
    <DropComment_ColonistMedicineDrop>Somebody has to cure you of any illness, right?</DropComment_ColonistMedicineDrop>
    <DropComment_ColonistSocialDrop>Somebody has to negotiate with all those savages on your planet, right?</DropComment_ColonistSocialDrop>
    <DropComment_ColonistIntellectualDrop>Somebody has to improve your standard of living (we can't supply you with absolutely everything this far out), right?</DropComment_ColonistIntellectualDrop>
    <DropComment_ColonistArtisticDrop>Somebody has to be a court jester (and occasionally do art), right? Just be warned - we can't test the skill of such a candidate.</DropComment_ColonistArtisticDrop>
    <DropComment_ColonistRomanceFemaleDrop>Maidenless? Just request one!</DropComment_ColonistRomanceFemaleDrop>
    <DropComment_ColonistRomanceMaleDrop>Unwed maiden? Just request one!</DropComment_ColonistRomanceMaleDrop>

    <!-- Biotech -->
    <DropComment_BabyFoodDrop>Do you have children there? In that case, I'll even give you a little more food for the kids.</DropComment_BabyFoodDrop>
    <DropComment_VampiresFoodDrop>I hope it's just someone needs a blood transfusion. We don't usually receive such requests, be careful with such things.</DropComment_VampiresFoodDrop>
    <DropComment_BabyClothesDrop>Shirt? Check. Pants. Check. Helmet and backpack... Why do you need a kid-sized helmet?</DropComment_BabyClothesDrop>

</LanguageData>